(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-27T21:41:29.174016",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
イェーイ！みんなこんにねー！
Yay! Hello everyone!
というわけで、3月2日お誕生日があるの、ももすずねね…イェーイ！
So, my birthday is on March 2nd! Momosuzu Nene... Yay!
みんなお誕生日迎えましたー！みんなありがとー！
My birthday has arrived! Thank you everyone!
今日はハッシュタグ「桃鈴ねね誕生日2022」でたくさんつぶやいてください！
Today, please tweet a lot using the hashtag #MomosuzuNeneBirthday2022!
見たい！トレンド入りしたところがみたいなというわけでたくさんツイートお願いします！
I want to see it trending, so please send lots of tweets!
今日はですね、2部構成で行っていきたいと思います！
Today, we're going to do a two-part structure!
第1部がですね、ゲストさんをお呼びしてね、もう収録が終わっていますので
Part 1 will feature some guests. Recording is already finished,
そちらをみんなで見ていきたいと思います！
so let's all watch that together!
そして第2部はですね、MCのゲストの人をお呼びして生のソロパートを行っていきたいと思いますので
And Part 2 will feature MC guests and a live solo segment,
よかったら1時間お付き合いいただけると嬉しいです！
so I'd be happy if you could join us for an hour!
みんなステージ見て、ステージ！じゃあ見て！わー、すごい！
Everyone look at the stage! Look at that! Wow, amazing!
今回ね、ねねの誕生日のためにスタジオスタッフさんたちがね、ちょっとねね仕様にアレンジしたステージを作ってくれましたー！
The studio staff specially arranged this stage just for Nene's birthday!
あ、みんなコメントいっぱいありがとうー！
Ah, thank you all so much for the comments!
というわけで早速ですね、まずはゲストパートを一緒に見ていきたいと思いますので
So right away, let's watch the guest part together first.
客席を映さないとさ、ゲストパート見れないからさ、みんなのこと客席にぶっ投げていきたいと思います！
Since we need to show the audience seats to see it, I'm going to throw you all into the audience!
それではゲストパートいってみよー！みんな行ってこーい！
Well then, let's go to the guest part! Off you go!
始まるよー！
It's starting~!
めーるるるるるるるるるるる〜
Merurururururu...
めでお☆いんぱくと
Medeo☆Impact
宇宙にきらめ〜く 流れ星〜☆
Sparkling in space, a shooting star☆
まじ〜かるじぇ〜っとで、て〜きを〜撃つ〜
With a magical jet, strike down the enemy~
魔法のくにから 地球のために
From the magic land, for the sake of Earth
落ちて流れて〜 こんにちは〜
Falling and flowing, hello~
星くずういちメルル〜♪
Stardust Uichi Meruru~♪
しゅ〜てぃんぐすた〜 しゅ〜てぃんぐすた〜
Shooting star, shooting star
あなたの胸に飛び込んで行くの
I'll dive straight into your heart
隕石よりも（キラッ☆）
Brighter than a meteor (Kira☆)
巨大なパワーで
With massive power
あなたのハートをねらい撃つの
Aiming straight for your heart!
だから わたしの全力 全開魔法
That's why my full-power all-out magic!
逃げずに ちゃんと受け止めてよね〜
Make sure you catch it without running away~
めーるめるる めるるめるる〜
Mel Mel ruru, Mel ruru meruru~
架空を舞い飛ぶ
Flying through the fictitious sky,
女の子
a girl
まじかるろっどで ほしをうつ
shooting stars with a magical rod!
日本のすみから 宇宙のために
From the corners of Japan, for the universe,
跳ねて 暴れて こんにちは 星くずういちメルル〜
bounce, go wild, hello! Stardust Witch Melru~
しゅ〜てぃんぐすた〜
Shooting star...
あなたの胸に飛び込んで行くの
I'm diving right into your chest!
太陽よりも 熱いカラダで
With a body hotter than the sun,
あなたのすべて焼き尽くすの
I'll burn away everything you are!
だから わたしの全力 全開魔法
That's why my full-power all-out magic!
逃げずに ちゃんと受け止めてよね〜
Make sure you catch it without running away~
銀河の果てから 流星に乗って 落ちて暴れてタイショーだ！
From the edge of the galaxy, riding a shooting star, falling and going wild!
お待たせ！ 夢の続きの仲間占める
Kept you waiting! Rounding up companions for the dream's continuation.
まじかるろっどで 星くずういちメルル！ 行きます！
With a magical rod, Stardust Witch Meluru! Here we go!
しゅ〜てぃんぐすた〜
Shooting star...
あなたの胸に飛び込んで行くの
I'm diving right into your chest!
流星よりも 強い気持ちで
With feelings stronger than a shooting star,
あなたのココロ抱きしめるの
I'm holding your heart tight!
だから わたしの全力 全開魔法
That's why my full-power all-out magic!
逃げずに ちゃんと受け止めてよね〜
Make sure you catch it without running away~
めーるめるる めるるめるる〜
Mel Mel ruru, Mel ruru meruru~
御伽話は
Fairytales are
さっき死んだみたい
like they died just moments ago.
煉瓦の病棟で
In a brick ward,
うまく歌えなくて
unable to sing well,
霧に煙る夜
on a night shrouded in fog,
浮かべ赤い月
a red moon floats.
ほらみて私を
Look at me,
目を逸らさないで
don't look away.
黒い鉄格子の中で
Inside the black iron bars,
私は生まれてきたんだ
I was born.
悪意の代償を願い 望むがままにお前に お前に お前に
Wishing for the price of malice, as you desire, to you, to you, to you...
さあ与えよう正義を 壊して 壊される前に
Now, I shall grant you justice, destroying before being destroyed.
因果の代償を払い 共に行こう
Pay the price of cause and effect, let's go together,
名前のない怪物
Nameless Monster.
耳鳴りがしてる
My ears are ringing,
鉄条網うるさくって
the barbed wire is too noisy.
思い出せないの
I can't remember
あの日の旋律
that day's melody.
雨はまだやまない
The rain still hasn't stopped.
何にも見えないの
I can't see a thing...
ほらみて こんなに
Look, it's gotten
大きくなったの
this big now.
黒い雨 降らせこの空
Black rain, fall upon this sky.
私は 生まれないもの
I am a being that was never born,
ひび割れたノイローゼ
a cracked neurosis.
愛す同罪の傍観者達に
To the complicit bystanders who love—
さあ今 震え正義を消せない
Now tremble, justice cannot be erased.
傷を抱きしめて この身体を受け入れ共に行こう
Embrace the wounds, accept this body and let's go together,
名前のない怪物
a nameless monster.
神は告げる
God proclaims
神ハ告ゲル
真ノ世界ヲ
the true world...
黒い鉄格子の中で
Inside the dark iron bars,
私は 生まれてきたんだ
I was born into this world.
悪意の代償を願え
Pray for the price of malice,
望むがままに お前に お前に お前に
as you wish, upon you, upon you, upon you!
さあ 与えよう正義を
Now, let us bestow justice,
壊して 壊される前に
destroying it before it is destroyed.
因果の代償を払い 報いよ
Pay the price of karma and receive your reward,
名もなき怪物
nameless monster.
黒い雨 降らせこの空
Black rain, fall upon this sky.
私は 生まれないもの
I am a being that was never born,
ひび割れたノイローゼ
a cracked neurosis.
愛す同罪の傍観者達に
To the complicit bystanders who love—
さあ今 震え正義を消せない
Now tremble, justice cannot be erased.
傷を抱きしめて この身体を受け入れ共に行こう
Embrace the wounds, accept this body and let's go together,
名前のない怪物
a nameless monster.
ありがとーー！おつかれー！
Thank you so much! Great job!
なんかさ、誕生日のだいたい物をお聞きいただきました！
We just performed our birthday track for you!
ありがとー！ナスピス！
Thank you! Naspisu!
そう、なくしたピッチね。
Yeah, the lost pitch, right?
お誕生日おめでとう！ありがとう！
Happy birthday! Thank you!
二人とも来てくれてありがとう！いぇーい！
Thank you both for coming! Yay!
いや、今回もね、ダンス頑張りましたね。
Man, we worked really hard on the dancing this time too.
今回練習期間がすごく短かった！
The practice period was super short this time!
でもさ、みんなダンス覚えるの早いよね！
But you know, everyone learns dances so fast!
家でめっちゃやってきたんだなって。
It showed how much they practiced at home.
ここね、これね、これめっちゃ難しかった！
This part right here, this was super hard!
難しいんだよね、このステップ。先生がさ、ガルガルやるからさ...
It's so hard, this step. The instructor does it like grrr...
できるわけないじゃん！って。
Like 'There's no way we can do that!'
マッチがね、この...こう...こう持ちが...
Machi was like, this... holding like this...
でもかっこよかったと思う！
But I think it looked really cool!
えもう！えもう！えもうえもう！
Eh mou! Eh mou! Eh mou!
疲れちゃって...声裏返っちゃった！
I got so tired... my voice cracked!
いや大変だったよ、やっぱり！
Man, it was tough after all!
でもちづねねはね、今からもちっとまだ...
But Chizunene still has a bit more...
あ、そうだよ！続くわ！
Ah, that's right! It continues!
二人とまた踊れて本当に嬉しかった！ありがとう！また踊ろう！
I'm so happy I got to dance with you two again! Thank you! Let's dance again!
次もね ダンスよろしく
Thanks for the dance next time!
次のダンスもよろしくー！
And thanks for the next dance too!
え、次、ちょっと待って。
Hold on, for the next one...
ちょっと次の話をするとさ、次はどんな感じの踊りたい？歌いたい？
Speaking of the next one, what kind of vibe do you want to dance or sing?
えー？
Hmm?
え、3人で？
Huh, the three of us?
なんか、あのー、K-POPみたいなやつやりたい！
I wanna do something like K-POP!
でもそれもやっぱりダンスまた激しいやつ？ 激しいやつよ！
But that'd be another intense dance, right? Super intense!
なんか、ズンズンズンズン デュエンデクで みたいないうやつ。
Like, zun-zun-zun-zun, du-en-deku-de style.
いや、おりそうじゃん、やだ！ え、おりそうじゃでしょ？
No way! But you'd be able to do it, right?
ないかな？あるかもしれない！ あ、あるかな？
Would you? Maybe!
やりたいね、またね。 やりたい！
I'd love to do it again!
またお楽しみに！ また次のダンスをお楽しみに！ お楽しみに！
Look forward to the next dance!
もう朝も昼も今日も明日もくじけない！
Morning, noon, today, and tomorrow, we won't give up!
うおーーーーーー！
Whoaaaaa!
つまりはいつもくじけない！
In short, we never give up!
ああ……今日もしっぱい うまくいかない
Ah... today's a failure too, nothing's going right.
へこんだけれど くじけない そんな日もあるよ 結構ある
Feeling down, but we won't give up! Days like that happen, quite a lot.
半泣きだけど ハッピーです！
Crying a bit, but we're happy!
こしたんたん狙い撃ち めちゃでか野望持ってマス
Plotting secretly, taking aim, holding huge ambitions!
人生なんて ほらほらね 谷あり谷あり……
Life is, see, full of ups and downs...
なんで？ 前だけを見てススメ
Why? Just look ahead and move forward!
どっちが前だ！？ 無限讃歌
Which way is front!? Infinite hymn!
つまりくじけない！ 今日がダメでも
In short, we won't give up! Even if today's no good,
明日はJust hit “傷心”からの 一歩“前進”
Tomorrow's Just hit, taking a step forward from heartbreak,
そんでもって今“変身”
And now, transforming right now!
もっとカッコつけ前向き いつもくじけない
Being cooler and more positive, always never giving up!
あきらめなんて 辞書にない
Giving up isn't in our dictionary!
結局結局なんだ 壁はちょっと高いけど
After all, the wall is a bit high, but...
もう朝も昼も今日も明日もくじけない！ うおーーーーーー！
Morning, noon, today, and tomorrow, we won't give up! Whoaaaaa!
また一歩進み 一歩戻る せつないけれど くじけない
Taking a step forward, a step back, it's bittersweet, but we won't give up!
強がりモードは解けないけど ゴメンはちゃんと言えますです……
Can't drop the act, but we can say sorry properly...
結果ぜんぜん出ない日々 それも全部計算のうち（？）
Days with no results at all, is that all part of the plan?!
ぐーお腹が減った 飯テロめ……
Guu, I'm hungry. Such food terrorism.
今に見てろ 食べ放題 しゅちにくりん もうすぐっと……！
Just you wait, all-you-can-eat, shuchinikurin, almost there...!
ネバーギブアップ つまりくじけない 今日があるから明日がある
Never give up, in short we won't give up, because today exists, tomorrow exists.
1000回無理？じゃあ 1001回！ 限界なんてない！
1000 times impossible? Then 1001 times! There are no limits!
“後悔”ばっかしちゃうけど
Regretting things constantly,
全身全霊かけて毎日を生きてます！
Living every day with all our heart and soul!
泣いてる？ 泣いてない くじけた？ 全然くじけてないです
Crying? Not crying. Broken down? Not broken down at all.
不幸 不運 不満 飛んでけ もうどこか遠く空へ
Misfortune, bad luck, dissatisfaction, fly away, far off into the sky.
さあ夢を叶えよう 夢は叶うよ 準備は完了
Come on, let's make dreams come true, dreams will come true, preparation complete.
さあ急げ急げ急げ急げ急げ急げ Go Goooooooo!
Now hurry hurry hurry hurry hurry hurry Go Goooooooo!
無限讃歌 つまりくじけない 今日がダメでも 明日はJust hit
Infinite hymn, in short we won't give up, even if today's no good, tomorrow's Just hit.
“傷心”からの一歩“前進” そんでもって今“変身”
Taking a step forward from heartbreak, and now transforming right now!
もっとカッコつけ前向き いつもくじけない あきらめなんて 辞書にない
Being cooler and more positive, always never giving up, giving up isn't in our dictionary!
結局結局なんだ 壁はちょっと高いけど
After all, the wall is a bit high, but...
もう朝も昼も今日も明日もくじけない！ うおーーーーーー！
Morning, noon, today, and tomorrow, we won't give up! Whoaaaaa!
手を上げて Clap your hands 海の向こうまで Clap your hands 届きますように
Raise your hands, Clap your hands, across the sea, Clap your hands, may it reach you.
手を叩こう 手を叩こう ほら一緒に Everybody
Let's clap our hands, let's clap our hands, look, together, Everybody.
Clap your hands 空の向こうまで Clap your hands 響きますように
Clap your hands, to the other side of the sky, Clap your hands, may it resonate.
手を叩こう 手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands, let's clap our hands.
光りさす 僕たちの未来
Our shining future.
始めようか さあ diving
Let's start, c'on, diving
待っても意味ない timing
There's no use in waiting, timing
あの魚みたいに swimming
Like those fish, swimming
swimming 引き寄せるの lighting
swimming, the lighting draws us in
まだ見えないよ maybe
You still can't see it yet, maybe
この先には何があるの?
What lies ahead of us?
まだ早いよ take it
It's still early, take it
追いつくまで shaking
Shaking until we catch up
でもたまに止まって thinking
But sometimes, stop and think, thinking
変えてみせるさ change
I'll show you how to change
踏み出すのさ stepping
Stepping forward
掴んでみせるよ キラキラ my dream
I'll grasp my sparkling dream
叶う日まで story 繋ぐから
Connected to the story until it comes true
だって君にずっと見てほしいから
Because I want you to watch me always
手を上げて clap your hands
Raise your hands, clap your hands
海の向こうまで clap your hands
Across the sea, clap your hands
届きますように 手を叩こう
May it reach you, let's clap our hands
手を叩こう ほら一緒に
Let's clap our hands, come on together
everybody clap your hands
空の向こうまで clap your hands
Across the sky, clap your hands
響きますように 手を叩こう
May it resound, let's clap our hands
手を叩こう 光射す 僕たちの未来
Let's clap our hands, our future illuminated by light
今日はいらない ブレーキ
Don't need brakes today
理性壊せ breaking
Break your sanity, breaking
何時でもいいでしょ? 四六時中
Anytime is fine, right? 24/7
君は何を feeling?
What are you feeling?
解き放て sparking
Release the sparking
暗闇に放つ レーザービーム
Laser beams unleashed into the darkness
光らせて stage 作るから
Illuminating the stage as we build it
だって君にもっと見てほしいから
Because I want you to gaze at me even more
手を上げて clap your hands
Raise your hands, clap your hands
海の向こうまで clap your hands
Across the sea, clap your hands
届きますように 手を叩こう
May it reach you, let's clap our hands
手を叩こう ほら一緒に
Let's clap our hands, come on together
everybody clap your hands
空の向こうまで clap your hands
Across the sky, clap your hands
響きますように 手を叩こう
May it resound, let's clap our hands
手を叩こう 光射す 僕たちの未来
Let's clap our hands, our future illuminated by light
重なる wave 世界を揺らせ
Let overlapping waves shake the world!
終わりがあることくらい I know
I already know that there's an end to everything
でもまだまだ泳ぎ足りないの
But I still haven't had enough of swimming around yet
give me crazy
まるで lazy?
Like lazy?
次元混ざり合うの 全て塗り替える blue
Dimensions intertwine, recoloring everything in blue
手を上げて clap your hands
Raise your hands, clap your hands
海の向こうまで clap your hands
Across the sea, clap your hands
届きますように 手を叩こう
May it reach you, let's clap our hands
手を叩こう ほら一緒に
Let's clap our hands, come on together
everybody clap your hands
空の向こうまで clap your hands
Across the sky, clap your hands
響きますように 手を叩こう
May it resound, let's clap our hands
手を叩こう 光射す 僕たちの未来
Let's clap our hands, our future illuminated by light
今日はいらない ブレーキ
Don't need brakes today
理性壊せ breaking
Break your sanity, breaking
何時でもいいでしょ? 四六時中
Anytime is fine, right? 24/7
君は何を feeling?
What are you feeling?
解き放て sparking
Release the sparking
暗闇に放つ レーザービーム
Laser beams unleashed into the darkness
光らせて stage 作るから
Illuminating the stage as we build it
だって君にもっと見てほしいから
Because I want you to gaze at me even more
手を上げて clap your hands
Raise your hands, clap your hands
海の向こうまで clap your hands
Across the sea, clap your hands
届きますように 手を叩こう
May it reach you, let's clap our hands
手を叩こう ほら一緒に
Let's clap our hands, come on together
everybody clap your hands
空の向こうまで clap your hands
Across the sky, clap your hands
響きますように 手を叩こう
May it resound, let's clap our hands
手を叩こう 光射す 僕たちの未来
Let's clap our hands, our future illuminated by light
重なる wave 世界を揺らせ
Let overlapping waves shake the world!
終わりがあることくらい I know
I already know that there's an end to everything
でもまだまだ泳ぎ足りないの
But I still haven't had enough of swimming around yet
give me crazy
まるで lazy?
Like lazy?
次元混ざり合うの 全て塗り替える blue
Dimensions intertwine, recoloring everything in blue
手を上げて clap your hands
Raise your hands, clap your hands
海の向こうまで clap your hands
Across the sea, clap your hands
届きますように 手を叩こう
May it reach you, let's clap our hands
手を叩こう ほら一緒に
Let's clap our hands, come on together
everybody clap your hands
空の向こうまで clap your hands
Across the sky, clap your hands
響きますように 手を叩こう
May it resound, let's clap our hands
手を叩こう 光射す 僕たちの未来
Let's clap our hands, our future illuminated by light
手を上げて clap your hands
Raise your hands, clap your hands
海の向こうまで clap your hands
Across the sea, clap your hands
届きますように 手を叩こう
May it reach you, let's clap our hands
手を叩こう ほら一緒に
Let's clap our hands, come on together
everybody clap your hands
空の向こうまで clap your hands
Across the sky, clap your hands
響きますように 手を叩こう
May it resound, let's clap our hands
手を叩こう 光射す 僕たちの未来
Let's clap our hands, our future illuminated by light
手を上げて clap your hands
Raise your hands, clap your hands
海の向こうまで clap your hands
Across the sea, clap your hands
届きますように 手を叩こう
May it reach you, let's clap our hands
手を叩こう ほら一緒に
Let's clap our hands, come on together
everybody clap your hands
空の向こうまで clap your hands
Across the sky, clap your hands
響きますように 手を叩こう
May it resound, let's clap our hands
手を叩こう 光射す 僕たちの未来
Let's clap our hands, our future illuminated by light
はーい！というわけでいかがでしたでしょうかゲストパート！
Hi! So how was the guest part?
皆さん改めてお祝いしてくれてありがとうございます！
Thank you everyone so much for celebrating with me again!
先輩たちみんな来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you all my senpais for coming!
そしてですね、ここからはですね生でお届けしていきたいと思っているのですが
And from here on, we'd like to deliver the rest live, but...
なんと先ほどね、あの初めてのね、5人でのBLUE CLAPPERやったでしょ？
You know, earlier we performed "BLUE CLAPPER" with all five of us for the very first time!
BLUE CLAPPER歌ってホロメンのみんなに来てもらってます！みんなねえのお祝いしに来ちゃってー！
We sang "BLUE CLAPPER" and had everyone come join us to celebrate Nene!
Happy birthday to you...
Happy birthday dear Nene...
ありがとう！
Thank you!
4人でね 初めてしたりとかかな？
Is this the first time doing it with four people?
そう、今回初めて4人でやったんですけど、ちょねねねお気に入りのとこがあって発表したいの。
Right, we did it with four of us for the first time, and Nene has a favorite part she wants to share.
オマルのラップの
Omaru's rap...
悪いオマルが訪るくらいのすでに愛の
"The bad Omaru visiting, already love..."
悪いオマルが歌ったの？
"Bad Omaru sang it?"
めっちゃ面白いじゃん
"That's hilarious!"
そこは笑ってない！オマルが、私、悪くなります！
"Don't laugh at that part! Omaru goes, 'I'm turning bad!'"
悪くなる、悪くなるって、悪くないのに、そうにする瞬間があるのね。
"She says she's turning bad, but she wasn't bad, there's that moment she acts like it."
じゃあ、そこまでめっちゃ普通だったのに急に、わる、わる、悪くなるって使って、めっちゃ悪くなる。
"So, up to that point it was super normal, then suddenly she uses 'bad, bad, turning bad,' and it gets super bad."
あれ本当好きでね。
"I really love that part."
こことかめっちゃ綺麗に揃って本当に良かった！
"And places like here matched so cleanly, it was really great!"
そう。めちゃめちゃ揃ったそこね。すごかった！
"Yeah. They matched so much there. It was amazing!"
ビスパッ、ビスパッ、ビスパッ。
"Bish-bash, bish-bash, bish-bash."
ここだけは合わせようにしてね。
"Just make sure to match this part."
そうそうそう。でもようやく、だね、本当に。
"Right, right, right. But finally, truly."
そうだよ！本当ありがとう！
"That's right! Thank you so much!"
あのさ、次からさ、ちょっとね、ソロ曲が始まるんだけど、
"And you know, starting next, a solo song begins, but"
ちょっと次の1曲さ、絶対盛り上がる曲だからさ、みんなにここにいてほしいんだよね、ねね。
"the next song is definitely a hype song, so we want everyone to stay right here, Nene."
途中退場あり。
"Midway exit allowed."
え、なんで？退場するの？違う違う！なんか変な、ちゃんと、ちゃんとした曲だったらずっと「おおっ」て聞いていくんだけど。
"Eh, why? You're exiting? No, no! If it's a weird, proper song, we'd keep going 'Ooh' and listening, but..."
え、ちゃんとステージ上？ステージ上に！そっか！
"Eh, properly on stage? On stage! I see!"
とってもいい曲ね、あの絶対ね、あの、ちょっと1人じゃ恥ずかしくってできない曲やるじゃん。
"It's a really great song, you know, one that's too embarrassing to do alone, right?"
恥ずかしい曲なの？
"An embarrassing song?"
え、でも、ここまで言われると、ここまで言われると帰りたくなってきた。
"Eh, but hearing it this much, being told this much makes me want to go home."
だからみんな自由にしてていいからさ、その代わりに、
"So everyone can do whatever they want, but in exchange,"
何しててもいいの？スマホ触ってもいい？
"We can do anything? Even touch our phones?"
ちょっと退出してもいい？
"Can we step out for a bit?"
いいよ！ツイートしてて！エゴサしとくわ！
"Sure! Tweet away! I'll do some ego-searching!"
エゴサはちゃんとするの、じゃあ。
"So you'll properly ego-search."
誕生日タグでエゴサして？
"Ego-search with the birthday tag?"
エゴサして？
"Ego-search?"
うん。じゃあみんな各自、じゃあ好きに。好きに。
"Yeah. Then everyone do as you like. Freely."
ねね、ちょっとお水飲みに行くからさ。
"Nene is going to go grab some water."
いや、それ、それ感じのやつじゃん。
"Wait, that's... that kind of thing."
え、オマル？オマル愛のって、オマルも愛のってしてくれるって信じてるよ。
"Eh, Polka? Polka, I believe you'll do the 'Ai no...' with me."
え、だって、そういう感じじゃないの？あ、こういう感じじゃあ、こういう感じで、うっ、やっ、やっ、やっ！
"Eh, wait, isn't it that kind of vibe? Ah, like this, like this, ugh, ya, ya, ya!"
あ、そうそう、いいね！いいね！
"Ah, yes, yes, nice! Nice!"
あれ？あれ二人？
"Huh? Huh, the two of them?"
なんてさ、ネネがお水飲みに行く、あれ？え？あれ何あれ？
"Why is Nene going to get water... Huh? Eh? What is that?"
ちゃんと聞いてるから！エゴサしてるから！
"We're listening properly! We're ego-searching!"
エゴサしてるから！
"We're ego-searching!"
エゴサ、エゴサするわ！
"Ego-searching, I'm ego-searching!"
足しながら聞いてます。わかった！じゃあ、ちょっと
"Listening while adding more. Understood! Then, um..."
心を込めて歌っていただきます！お、えーぞ！
"Please sing it with all your heart! Oh, awesome!"
それでは聴いてください。「チチをモゲ！」
"Now then, please listen. 'Chichi wo Moge!'"
チッチッチッチ おっぱい ボインボイ～ン
Boobs - boobs - boobs - boobs bouncing bouncing
モゲ モゲ モゲ モゲ チチをモゲ！
Moge - moge - moge - moge, pull the chichi!
さあアイノデシでねみんな一緒にアイノデシしてください！
Now, let's do the "Ai no deshi" together everyone!
今日はツイッターでみんなみんなのチチをモゲたいと思います！
Today on Twitter, I want to milk everyone's chichi!
モゲ モゲ モゲ モゲ チチをモゲ モゲ ザ・インポッシブル モゲ！
Moge - moge - moge - moge, pull the chichi! Moge, the impossible moge!
モゲ ポロロン プヨン モゲ まんまる チッチッチ
Moge, porolon, puyon, moge, round, chitchitchi
三角 おっぱい ロケット ボイ～ン やさしく
Triangle, boobs, rocket, boyn, gently
いきなり 微妙に 連続 モゲ モゲ モゲ モゲ おおーっ！
Suddenly, subtly, continuously, moge, moge, moge, moge, oooh!
チッチッチッチ おっぱい ボインボイ～ン
Boobs - boobs - boobs - boobs bouncing bouncing
モゲ モゲ モゲ モゲ チチをモゲ モゲ！
Moge - moge - moge - moge, pull the chichi! Moge!
みんな、ナイスアイノデシでありがとうみんな！ナイスアイノデシでしたー！
Everyone, thank you for the nice "ai no deshi"! That was a nice "ai no deshi"!
次はシシラビのチチを揉んでいきたいと思います！
Next, we're going to milk Shishirabi's chichi!
モゲ モゲ モゲ モゲ チチをモゲ！
Moge - moge - moge - moge, pull the chichi!
モゲ ポロロン プヨン モゲ モゲ パイン ボイン モゲ
Moge, porolon, puyon, moge, moge, pain, boin, moge
しましま チッチッチ おさるのおっぱい バズーカボイ～ン
Striped, chitchitchi, monkey's boobs, bazooka boyn
今日も 明日も とにかく 毎日 モゲ モゲ モゲ モゲ うおおーっ！
Today too, tomorrow too, anyway every day, moge, moge, moge, moge, oooh!
チッチッチッチ おっぱい ボインボイ～ン
Boobs - boobs - boobs - boobs bouncing bouncing
モゲ モゲ モゲ モゲ チチをモゲ モゲ！
Moge - moge - moge - moge, pull the chichi! Moge!
まてまてまてまてまてまて捕まえて
Wait wait wait wait wait wait, catch me!
捕まえてごらん
Catch me if you can!
早歩き
Walking fast!
捕まえてごらん
Catch me if you can!
いや、そこはほら、いいよ
No, come on, that's fine!
あはははは、ちゃんとツイートしてくれたかな？
Hahaha, I wonder if they tweeted properly?
チッチッチッチッおっぱい
Chicchi chicchi oppai!
ぼいんぼいん
Boin boin!
チッチッチッチッおっぱい、せいの、ぼいんぼいん
Chicchi chicchi oppai, ready, boin boin!
よいしょ、はい！
Heave ho, right!
チッチッチッチッおっぱい
Chicchi chicchi oppai!
ぼいんぼいん
Boin boin!
チッチッチッチッおっぱい、ぼいんぼいん
Chicchi chicchi oppai, boin boin!
踊り狂え！
Dance like crazy!
チチをもげ、もげ、もげ、もげ、チチをもげ！
Pluck the boobs, pluck, pluck, pluck, pluck them!
疲れた…
I'm tired...
チチをもげ、もげ、もげ！
Pluck the boobs, pluck, pluck, pluck!
チチを、もげ！
Pluck the boobs!
もげ！
Pluck!
やられちゃった！お前らうるさい！
We got beaten! You guys are noisy!
ありがとうございました！いやもう絶対やりたかったんだよ。
Thank you very much! No, I really wanted to do this.
3人とも踊って頂けまして、これなんなの？
All three of you danced, what is this?
ブルークラリネットはさ、スマートな感じじゃん？でも、これは楽しんでやりたかったの。
Blue Clarinet is smart-looking, right? But I wanted to do this just for fun.
ブルークラリネットはやっぱ完成度が欲しかったけど、これは楽しんでやりたかったの！
Blue Clarinet needed perfection, but I wanted to do this just for fun!
ある種の完成度はあった。
There was a certain kind of perfection.
延長の電話大丈夫？延長、延長しといて。
Is the call extension okay? Extend it, extend it.
ちょっとごめんな、みんなに言うけど、これネネの生誕祭だからね！
Sorry everyone, I have to say this, but this is Nene's birthday!
本当はね、みんなカラオケとかなくてさ、ここライブのステージでみんな見てるの今！
Actually, there's no karaoke, everyone's watching right here on the live stage!
え、コメント見てる？イエーイ、イエーイ！楽しかったな！
Hey, are you watching the comments? Yay, yay! That was fun!
こっからね、まだあるんだけどね、こっからちょっと真剣パートだからちょっとみんな離れないで！
There's more from here, but this is a serious part, so everyone don't leave!
これなんだったの？なんかっていうかやっぱネネの生誕祭だからね！
What was this? Well, because it's Nene's birthday!
じゃあ恥ずかしいからみんな入って！
It's embarrassing, so everyone join in!
よし、揉んでけ！揉んでけ！見せない！シャツ、だめだめ！
Alright, massage away! Don't show it! Shirt, no no!
ありがとう！お疲れ様！ありがと、ありがと！
Thank you! Good job! Thanks, thanks!
はあ、みんな休憩してもらって、じゃあネネはね
Phew, everyone take a break, now Nene...
ちょっと次の曲に移らせて頂きたいと思います。ここからはね、ネネの超超真剣アイドルモードお聞きください！
I'd like to move on to the next song. From here on, please enjoy Nene's super-serious idol mode!
それでは次の曲行きたいと思います。プレシャス！
Now, let's go to the next song. Precious!
心が見えなくて
When I couldn't see your heart,
不安な日もあった
there were days when I was anxious.
誰かを愛する意味
The meaning of loving someone,
自分なりに決めた
I decided it for myself.
すべてを信じ抜くこと
It is to believe in everything completely.
I promise you
もう迷わない
I won't hesitate anymore.
強くなる...
I will become stronger...
あなたに証すよ
I will prove it to you.
逃げないで 向き合っていく
Facing forward without running away,
姿を見せてくれた to heart
you showed me your true self to heart.
信じよう ふたりだから 愛しあえる
Let's believe because we are two, we can love each other.
あの空へ 願いが届くように
So that our wish reaches that sky,
見つめあい 祈る two of us
looking into each other's eyes and praying, two of us.
ふたつ重ねた想いが 今 ひとつの形に変わる
The feelings we've layered now change into a single form.
Your precious love
傷つき 苦しむなら
If we are hurt and suffer...
分けあって
share it,
抱きしめ合おう
and hold each other tight,
もうひとりじゃないから
because you are not alone anymore,
全てを受け止めるよ
I will accept everything,
信じよう
Let's believe
ふたりだから
because we are two,
愛し合える
we can love each other
永遠に つないだ
eternally connected
この手を もう 離さない
this hand, I won't let go anymore
誓う two of us
swearing, two of us
ふたつ重ねた想いがいま
The feelings we've layered, now
ひとつの形に変わる
change into a single form
幼かった ひとりよがりの愛
It was a naive, self-centered love
今は 強く信じあえる
Now, we can believe in each other strongly
新しい始まり
a new beginning
I want to be one with you
信じよう
Let's believe
ふたりの
the two of us
今 愛し合い
now, loving each other
此処にいる
we are here
光が 満ちるように
so that light overflows
抱きしめる あなたを
I will embrace you
信じよう
Let's believe
ふたりだから
because we are two,
愛し合える
we can love each other
あの空へ
to that sky
願いが 届くように
so that our wish reaches
見つめあい
looking into each other's eyes
祈る two of us
praying, two of us
ふたつ重ねた想いがいま
The feelings we've layered, now
ひとつの形に変わる
change into a single form
Your precious love
みんなありがとう！
Thank you, everyone!
ちょっと間違えてごめんね。
Sorry for messing up a bit.
お客さんの脇から見てるの知ってるんだけど、笑わさないでって。
I know you guys are watching from the side, so don't make me laugh.
踊ってたりしたさっき。
You guys were dancing earlier.
みんなありがとう、ゴンドラも見てみてくれ。
Thank you everyone, check out the gondola too.
実はね、根っこと一緒にステージに立ちたくて、ゴンドラに根っこくっつけてもらったんだ。
Actually, I wanted to stand on stage together with Nekko, so I had Nekko attached to the gondola.
ありがとう！みんなこれからも一緒にアイドルのステージをやっていこうね。
Thank you! Everyone, let's continue doing idol stages together.
このあとゴンドラから降りるので一旦暗くなります。
After this, I'll get down from the gondola, so it'll get dark for a moment.
はーい、というわけで「Precious」をお聴きいただきました！
Alright, so that was "Precious"!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
イェイ！イェイ！
Yay! Yay!
両脇にねみんながいてくれてるんですよ今。
Everyone is right here on both sides right now.
手ふっちゃった。あ、根っこだのね。
I waved my hand. Ah, it's Nekko.
というわけで、なんとソロのパート次が、ラストの曲になるんですけど、
And so, surprisingly, the next solo part will be the last song...
Twitterのトレンド1位なんだって、みんなありがとう！つぶやいてくれてありがとうねみんな。
It's #1 on Twitter trends, thank you everyone! Thank you for tweeting about it, everyone.
次ね、私の大好きな神田沙也加さんの
Next, I'd like to sing a song from
曲から1曲歌わせていただきたいと思います。
my favorite Sayaka Kanda's songs.
それでは聞いてください、ブレイクビート・バーク！
Please listen, Break Beat Bark!
警報が響いて
The alarm is blaring,
包囲網でガンジガラメ
surrounded and trapped,
Checkmate 寸前
on the brink of checkmate,
Countdownが嫌いだな
how I hate that countdown!
勝手な欲望で踏みつけられたって
Even if I get trampled by my own selfish desires,
僕のセオリーじゃ答えは
by my theory, my answer is...
“No! Are you kidding me?”
僕の刻んだ記憶を
The memories I carved into you,
君と作り上げてきた現実を
the reality I created with you,
イレギュラーになんて奪わせるな
don't let them get robbed by irregularities.
Break Beat Bark!
まだ見えない未来って単純じゃないダンジョンみたい
The future is still out of sight, like a complex dungeon—
Can’t see… だけどHead up!
Can't see... but head up!
すぐそこさ “Never give up”
It's right there, “Never give up”!
パスワードはそれで十分なんだ
That's good enough for a password.
君と僕の純粋すぎる理想捨てられないね？ Heartbeat
You can't throw away that too-pure ideal of yours and mine, can you? Heartbeat
叫び出せ願いの限り
So cry out as long as you wish!
冗談じゃないって言う間に足を奪われ
Getting tripped up in the time it takes to say “I'm not joking,”
K.O.偽装で “YOU LOSE” ふざけてる！
I pretend to be K.O.'ed, getting a “You lose”... I'm just fooling around!
正々堂々逃げたって僕はここさもう手遅れだね
Even if you run away from what's fair and square, I'll still be here. It's already too late, isn't it?
“Yes, you are kidding me!”
守るべきはずの約束を
The promise you're supposed to keep,
その中で育ててきた希望を
the hope fostered from it,
違反させちゃいけないんだ
you mustn't let them get violated.
Break Beat Bark!
遠ざかって明日へルートがまたループみたい Long way round…
As it grew far away, the route to tomorrow seemed like a loop again, long way round...
だけどWake up! 朝が来て “Hello, my hope!”
But wake up! The morning is here, “Hello, my hope!”
変換不可能な意志があれば
If you have an inconvertible will,
君と僕で立ち向かう壁 熱くなるでしょ？ Heartbeat
then you'll get excited about the wall that you and I face, right? Heartbeat
叫び出す祈りを込めて
So I'll cry out with my prayers,
涙の落ちる音がした
the sound of falling tears echoed.
今も耳に響いている
It's still echoing in my ears now.
音の速さで助けに行くよ
I'll go help you at the speed of sound!
強くなれ
Be strong,
この振動誰かを救うため戦い抜くために
this vibration is for saving someone, for fighting to the end.
Break Beat Bark!
見えてきた未来って
The future came into sight—
単純じゃないダンジョンじゃない Let’s see!
it's not all that simple, but it isn't a dungeon, let's see!
そうさHead up! すぐそこさ “Never give up”
That's right, head up! It's right there, “Never give up”!
パスワードはもう必要ないんだ
We don't need a password anymore.
君と僕の純粋すぎる理想叶えなきゃないね？ Heartbeat
You have to fulfill that too-pure ideal of yours and mine, don't you? Heartbeat
叫び出せ願いの限り
So cry out as long as you wish!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
みんなまたね！かもしれない、かもしれない、かもしれない！
See you all again! Maybe, maybe, maybe!
みんなありがとー！
Thank you everyone!
最後の曲、ebb and flow聴いてください。
Please listen to our final song, ebb and flow.
降り積もる粉雪が舞う
Accumulating powdered snow falls,
諦めかけた夢がまだ
and the dream I was on the brink of giving up on
波打つ あの日のままで
ripples again, just like it did on that day.
変わらない笑顔見つめた
I fixed my gaze on your unchanging smile,
染まる頬に触れた風が
and a wind, having brushed your blushing cheeks,
空高く抜けただ
escaped up into the sky.
いつも見ていた。
I was always watching you.
近いようで遠くて。
You were so close, yet far away;
いつだって、届かない…
always out of my reach...
どうして?と
"Why?" —
問いかけた声も揺れる
even my asking voice quivers.
ゆらゆら水面に浮かんだ
The moon appearing on the water's surface,
月は何も語らない
is swaying to and fro, saying nothing.
「同じね」
"I guess we're the same, huh?"
握る手が痛い
I clench my hand so hard it hurts.
いたずらに風が吹く朝
Mischievous morning in the wind
樹々の葉がじゃれあう声に
along with the voice of the leaves on the trees
合わせて駆け出す君を
you running away
ただ夢中で追いかけてた
I was just chasing in a dream
その横顔が見てるのは
The profile you see is far away,
遥か遠く ここじゃなくて
not here, but far in the distance.
海が満ち、また引いていく夕凪
The sea fills and the evening calm pulls back again,
心の岸に打ち寄せられた
rushed to the shores of my heart.
決意は明日の光
The determination is tomorrow's light.
信じて
Believe.
ねぇ
Hey,
問いかけた声が響く
the voice I called out with echoes,
はらはらと一緒に夜空
fluttering together into the night sky,
駆けっていけば
if I keep running.
あの丘に日差しさす頃に
When the sunlight shines on that hill,
「見つけた」
"I found it."
願いは宝石 輝き出す
A wish is a sparkling jewel shining bright,
the ebb and flow of my mind...
the ebb and flow...
ありがとうございました！最後の曲ebb and flowでした！
Thank you very much! The last song was ebb and flow!
というわけで皆さん羽織のお披露目です！
So everyone, this is the debut of the haori!
てぇてぇ、かわいいでしょー？
It's so precious, isn't it cute?
いいでしょ、いいでしょー？
Isn't it? Isn't it?
とゆーわけで、これをね、５期生のみんなにも自慢したいと思うので、呼びたいと思います！
So, I want to show this off to all the 5th gen members, so I'd like to call them out!
え、自慢されたい５期生のみんなー！
Hey, all you 5th gen members who want to be shown off!
あ、ねぇ見てみて！かわいいでしょー？
Hey, look, look! Isn't it cute?
なんかさ、ねぇ、ちょっと待って。こっちこっちこっち。やだやだやだ。
Hey, wait a second. Come over here. No, no, no.
いや、待って。ねぇ、かさがさなんだけど。
Wait, why is it so rustly?
わぎ、頂戴よ、ねぇ。これかもー。
Hey Wagi, give it here. Is this it too?
あれ、ないね。
Huh, it's not here.
あれ？あれ？みんな？みんなごめん。
Huh? Huh? Everyone? Sorry everyone.
わぎは？お前らさむそうじゃん。
Where's Wagi? You guys look cold.
あの、よ、頂戴よ、これ。
Hey, give me this.
あの、がさがさして、今日来たばっかりなのに、裏表逆で。
It's rustly, and it just came today, and it's inside out.
え？みんな、ちょっとちょっとアップ、アップ、アップ。
Huh? Everyone, close-up, close-up, close-up!
ももに、ももがある！
Peaches on my peaches!
え、かわいい！
Ah, cute!
え、いいなー！かわいいでしょー？
Oh, nice! Isn't it cute?
かわいいでしょー？ありがとう！
Isn't it cute? Thank you!
とゆーわけでですね、ねねからお披露目があったのとともに、もうひとつ告知があります！
So, following Nene's reveal, we have one more announcement!
まんだい！なんと、ねねの、お誕生日の、グッズがでまーす！
Ta-da! Nene's birthday merchandise is coming out!
とゆーわけで詳細は、こちらと...
So details are right here...
詳細はね、今から発表していこうと思うんですけど、
I'm going to announce the details right now,
ちょっとね、もう書いてあるんだけど、１つずつ確認していきたいと思います！
it's already written here, but let's check them one by one!
あ、みんなこっち来て。あ、みんなこっちこい。
Ah, everyone come here. Come over here.
あのね、まず、今回もフルセットがあります！直筆サインあります！
First, we have the full set this time too! There's a hand-signed autograph!
あ、ちょっと見えっちゃ...
Ah, you can see it...
やめて！見せないでよ！見せないでよな！やった！
Stop! Don't show it! Don't show it! Yay!
とゆーわけで、１つずつ見ていきましょう、こちら！
So let's look at them one by one, right here!
まず、ラバーマットが出まーす！
First, the rubber mat is out!
わー、かわいい！
Wow, cute!
ねねね、ねねのイラストって、なもり先生リスペクトしてるんだけど。
Nene's illustrations... I respect Namori-sensei so much.
やめてください！やめてください！なもり先生リスペクトしてるんだけど。
Please stop! Please stop! I respect Namori-sensei.
今回ね、そのリスペクトしてる大好きな大好きな先生にね、お誕生日の記念のラバーマットを描いていただきました！
This time, that beloved, favorite teacher I respect drew this birthday commemorative rubber mat for me!
ねねがね、お部屋でなんか、音楽をこう...なんか、思い浮かべてるみたいで感じで。
It's like Nene in her room, thinking of music...
めっちゃねっこじゃん。
That's super Nekko.
そう、ねっこがめっちゃむぎゅってされてるの。
Yeah, Nekko is being squished so much.
なので、すごく可愛いのでよかったら詳細のページで確認してみてください！
So it's super cute, please check out the details page!
そして次のグッズ！
And the next merchandise!
次は、ネッコのトートバッグが出まーす！
Next, the Nekko tote bag is out!
やったー！で、みんな、よく見て、よく見て！
Yay! Everyone, look closely, look closely!
イラスト、ももすずねね！とゆーわけでですね、今回ねねが描き下ろしました！
Illustration by Momosuzu Nene! So Nene drew this herself!
描き下ろしっていうか、なんか普通にいつも描いてるやん。
Or rather than drawn specially, I just draw it normally like always.
え、ちがう！描き下ろし！
Eh, no! It's specially drawn!
いつも描いてる。お前らすっごいしょーこ、これ。
You always draw it. You guys are amazing.
待って待って、じゃあやめたい、やめたい、ここから。
Wait wait, then I wanna stop, stop right here.
ちょっといい感じだね、あのコウモリのネッコとか、そうそう。
It has a nice vibe, like that bat Nekko, right.
なんか隠れ、隠れオタクグッズみたいな感じでね。
It's like secret otaku merch.
使っていただけたらと思います！ねねの描き下ろしなんでよろしくお願いします！
I hope you'll use it! It's Nene's original drawing so please look forward to it!
ネッコのパンツが出まーす！
The Nekko pants are out!
イエーイ！イエーイなのかいな？
Yay! Is that a "Yay"?
え、見て、見て見て！超かわいいでしょ？
Eh, look, look at this! Isn't it super cute?
これが、ねねが、お尻にネッコの顔がある...そうそう、ねねがね、ネッコのみんなのお尻に引く...
This is... Nene has Nekko's face on the butt... right, Nene puts Nekko on everyone's butt...
どういう意味で見てるけどお前。
What kind of look is that you're giving me?
お前らどう、これ？なんか...
How is this, guys? Like...
いや、なんか、しょうばんみたいな感じだけど、でも日常使いグッズなんだよね？
Well, it feels like merchandise, but it's everyday use merch, right?
そうそう！今回ね、ユニセックス、女の子のね、Lサイズでも履けるようにユニセックスにいたしまして、なのでね、注意としてはね、こちらの方、開きませんので気をつけてください！
Right! This time it's unisex, so girls can wear it in L size too, so please note that the front doesn't open, be careful!
開かないの？開かないんです。だからパジャマ代わりにもしてくださーい。
It doesn't open? It doesn't open. So please use it as pajamas too.
そしてほんとに、実際に下着としても身につけて、みんなのお尻の下にはネッコがいるって思ったら面白いのでよろしくお願いします！
And really, wearing it as actual underwear, thinking Nekko is under everyone's butt is fun, so please!
で、コラボで、お揃いのパンツでーす！記念ってパンツ出した人...
And collaboration, matching pants! Who releases pants for an anniversary...
でもだって、運営さんからめちゃめちゃ批判を食ってね...
But you know, I got criticized so much by management...
やめろ！その話は！後で聞くから！人間に怒ってもらう！
Stop it! Don't talk about that! I'll hear it later! Scold her, human!
そしてフルセットをご購入してくれた方には、
For those who purchased the full set,
ねねのかきおろし直筆サイン入りポストカード……！
you'll get Nene's newly drawn, hand-signed postcard...
そろそろ呼ばない？
Should we call them out soon?
そう、今回はね、しかもね、あの、特定のボイスがつくんですけど、
That's right, and this time, what's more, it comes with a special voice,
普段ねねのASMRの枠ってちょっとおふざけしちゃうんだけどは、
normally in Nene's ASMR streams I tend to mess around a bit,
ガチマジASMRで挑んでいきます！
but this time I'm doing dead-serious ASMR!
そして直筆サインのポストカードではですね、前回、去年もお誕生日の時にやったんだけど、サインとはちょっとメッセージみたいな感じで書いていけたらいいなと思いますので、
And for the hand-signed postcards, like last year for my birthday, I hope to write them with a bit of a personal message alongside the signature,
皆さんよろしくお願いします！
so everyone please look forward to it!
みんなどう？ねねの今回のグッズ。
What do you all think of Nene's merch this time?
すごい！いい感じじゃん！
Amazing! It looks great!
パンツ履くでしょ？
You're gonna wear the pants, right?
お尻の…あ、ここにする！ここにする！
On the butt— ah, right here! Right here!
パンツすごい！これいいよね！
The pants are amazing! This is nice!
ネポラボで箱でしょ？
And it's a NEPOLABO box, right?
ネポラボで箱、ネポラボで…ネポラボでお揃いにするので、
A NEPOLABO box, NEPOLABO... since we're matching with NEPOLABO,
皆さんもお揃いにしてください！
everyone please match with us too!
開かないでしょ？
It doesn't open, right?
開かないの。今回それを招くよ。開かないの。
It doesn't open. I'll invite that this time. It doesn't open.
開かないので。
Since it doesn't open.
というわけでね、最後にねね、上着着たしね、みんなで可愛い写真撮って終わりにしたいです！
With that said, finally since Nene put on her jacket, I want to take a cute picture with everyone to wrap up!
いいですか？
Is that okay?
アップアップで可愛く撮ってください！
Take it nice and close up and cute!
あー、いいよ！いいよ！
Ah, nice! Awesome!
みんなありがとう！というわけで、今日のねねの配信はここまで！
Thank you everyone! With that, Nene's stream for today ends here!
皆さんたくさんお祝いしてくれてありがとう！
Thank you all so much for celebrating with me!
4人ともありがとう！4人じゃな…3人と…ありがとう！
Thank you all four! Not four... three and... thank you!
おめでとう！またね！お疲れ様でしたー！
Congrats! See you later! Great job everyone!